 i knew it, and i hired him anyway. i still can't stay, harvey. i know. i just want to stop lying to the people i love. this makes it look like forstman's payment never went to any offshore accounts. that's forgery. which is less of a crime than what you did. i had no choice. bullshit, you had no choice. you could've said no at any goddamn point along the way. one thing is for sure when all this is over, i'm gonna fire the shit out of you. i went to robert zane, and i asked him to give louis a job. you want to see if i can break my partnership agreement. if you can't do that, what the hell good are you? louis won't be going to zane, and neither will you. i'm here to ask you to take louis anyway. and why would i do that? if you do, i'll owe you one. mike ross doesn't forget anything. see, the reason he didn't recognize this is because he didn't go to harvard. you've been lying to me since the day mike ross arrived. i am your friend, louis. no, you're not. and don't you ever say that to me again. you might as well spit it out. you asked me what i wanted once before, and i told you, and then you told me that i couldn't have it. pearson. specter. litt. want to tell me what was so important i had to get back here? he knows. i know what you're thinking. why didn't donna tell you? i'll tell you why. because as my first official act as name as name partner, i told her not to. what? you heard me. you can look at her as long as you want. she can't help you. because my name's going up there first thing tomorrow. no, it isn't. yes, it is. but it won't be tomorrow. i'm not waiting just so you can. louis, i have to sell this to the senior partners. i can't just slap your name up there one morning. you did it for him. i didn't resign the week before. i don't care. louis. that's enough. this is going to take time, and while it does, you're going to keep this to yourself. bullshit. you're just trying to buy time so you can get out of this. i'm not trying to buy anything. we have an agreement, and this is for your own good. well, for your own good, you better remember what i'll do if this takes too long. please tell me you had no other choice. you know damn well i didn't. no, i don't. that's because you didn't see him. all he's ever thought about since the day he was born was getting this. so if i have to choose between giving it to him and going to jail. he really threatened that? he didn't just threaten it. he was going to do it. and what are we going to do? we're going to take it. we give him this, it is never gonna end. harvey, before you say another word to me, i want you to think about the fact that i just ate a big bowl of shit because you brought that kid into my house. and i had to take it, so you're going to take it. harvey. you don't need to say it. yeah, i do. louis came looking for you, and i didn't know what to do. he was gonna call sheila and tell her everything. i'd never seen him like that before. donna, this is not on you. yes, it is. he pressed me, and i broke. it doesn't matter, because he already knew. how can you know that? because i know louis, and i know you. and he couldn't have broken you unless he knew the truth already. so this is not your fault, and i never want to hear you say that again. i should've at least warned you before you got here. all that would have done was antagonize him even more because he would've known you did it. you did everything you could've done. okay. we have to tell mike. no, we don't. not now. harvey. look, i'll tell him in the morning. we just had a huge win, and i am not in the mood to ruin his night. louis. what are you doing here? they didn't tell you. tell me what? jessica made me name partner. but, uh. but? but? but what? i resigned in shame? well, that's all changed, and it's all because of you. remember this? no, you don't, because you can't remember something you never knew. cool to the end. well, it doesn't matter, because donna told me. and harvey. and jessica. when i told them that i knew you were a fraud, did they run from you like you were the plague. what do you want? i already got what i wanted from you. name partner. you must want something else. otherwise, you wouldn't be here. see, that's what i love about you, mike. almost always a step ahead. what i want from you is to know that you're dead at my law firm. you can't fire me. why would i fire you when i can break you? you see, i'm going to bury you under a mountain of shit so big you're going to be begging me to take it off. and all you have to do is say two simple words. the same two words that you let me say to harvey and jessica. i resign. louis. what are you doing here? leaving. that way i don't have to look at either one of you two liars. oh, my god, he knows. he doesn't just know. he's a name partner. see the money, wanna stay for your meal get another piece of pie for your wife everybody wanna know how it feel everybody wanna see what it's like i'll even eat a bean pie, i don't mind me and missy is so busy, busy making money all right all step back, i'm 'bout to dance suits x enough is enough original air date on january , the greenback boogie sync, corrected by elderman elder man. you know. yeah, i know. and a little heads up would've been nice. i wanted to give you the night. well, the night kind of got blown up when louis showed up at my apartment and said he was gonna break me. what do you want from me, mike? i want to know how you let him become name partner. would you rather we let him go to the police? i don't believe that louis would actually go to the police. he would because jessica said he would. so if you're here to say that we can figure some way out of it, that's not going to happen. he knows, and it's done. did you hear what i said? louis came to my apartment filled with rage, and he told me he was making it his personal mission to break me. then you make it your mission not to let him. harvey, he's name partner. did i ever tell you the story about the gym? i'm not really in the mood for a story right now. then you're going to hear it anyway. when i was a kid, my father put me in boxing camp. middle of summer, degrees. every day after sparring in that, they'd make you do laps and pull ups. they'd push you until you either threw up or passed out or both. anyone could leave at any point. all you had to do was quit. and let me guess, you didn't quit. i quit every goddamn day. i just never said it out loud. because no way was i gonna give them the satisfaction of breaking me. so i guess it's time for me to drop down and give louis . i think it's gonna be a little more than , buddy. i see you noticed i scraped your little associate title away. you scraped it away? yeah, just like i'm gonna scrape you away, starting with these. oh, louis, go ahead. give me all of the shittiest cases that you can find, but i'm telling you, it's not gonna break me. you overestimate yourself. did you think when i said i was going to bury you in shit, i meant legal work? no, no, no. you're not a lawyer, which means you must be a paralegal, and that's exactly the kind of work you're gonna be doing. louis, you can't do this. everyone out there thinks of me as a lawyer. and two days ago, they thought of me as someone who used to work here. look at us now. oh, and if you're thinking of crying to harvey. that would be a major mistake, because this is between you and me. what are you doing here? i'm here because i know you're angry and you're feeling betrayed, but i am not gonna let you throw our friendship away. i can't throw away something that never existed in the first place. louis. donna, we're not friends. we were never friends, because it was all based on a lie. so you think my giving you this and every other nice thing that i ever did for you was just to keep you from finding out about mike? no, i don't. but i do think if you had the chance to take back all those nice things you did in exchange for me never finding out about your little secret, you'd do it in a heartbeat. you want a chance to tell me the truth? go ahead. tell me the truth right now. and that answers my question. you know what, louis? it was a bullshit question designed to do nothing but make me feel like shit. mission accomplished. and now i'm gonna tell you what i told mike. you're dead to me. okay. you want to hate me? hate me. you want to hate mike? hate mike. but everybody at this firm can't be dead to you, because sooner or later, you're going to need someone. thank you, donna, but that someone isn't going to be you. donna said you wanted to see me. no, i didn't want to see you, i needed to see you. i know you're under a lot of stress, but that was a one time thing. i don't need you to do that to me. louis has already done it. what are you talking about? look at this. he's buried me in paralegal work. okay, that's bullshit. he can't treat you like that. rachel, i don't care how he treats me, all right? i can take it until he gets over this. but look at these deadlines. there's no way i can get all of this work done on time without your help. i will do whatever you need, but, mike, he is not going to get over it until you make him get over it. rachel, please. mike. the day after what happened in here happened, i shut you out. but then, a week later, you came to my door, and you said you weren't gonna let me go without a fight. that is not the same. i wanted you to fall in love with me. i was already in love with you, and you knew it. yeah, well, louis is a lot of things, but he's not in love with me. he used to be. you just have to make him remember that. okay, the first thing we need to do is finish all of this work. okay. unless, of course, that offer still stands. i don't recall making an offer. you did say whatever i need. that's not what i meant. and then you said never take no for an answer, so. lock the doors. are you serious. take yes for an answer. i'm locking the door. louis, you sounded urgent on the phone. what's going on? i'll tell you what's going on. i'm back at pearson specter. what? i don't understand. let me explain it to you. i just became name partner. louis, this is amazing. i'm so happy for you. okay, well, you can keep being happy for me, but you better start being happy for you, because i'm bringing you back. what? i. oh. katrina amanda bennett, will you be my associate? louis marlowe litt, i will be your associate. again. you've just made me the happiest attorney on earth. when do we consummate our new preexisting relationship? as soon as my new position is official. wait, why isn't it official? i can't tell you that. louis, i think i've more than proven you can trust me. oh, are you kidding me? you're the only one i can trust. it's not that. it's just. okay, louis, you don't need to tell me. but if you won't tell me, and they won't tell the world, something's wrong. katrina, i know what i'm doing. and jessica knows what she's doing, which is playing you for a fool. harvey, i was just gonna call you. i'll save you the trouble. we're bringing louis litt back to the firm. that doesn't matter. because that call was to tell you i'm hiring him, and you owe me. bullshit. you calling me a liar? i'm not calling you anything, but you are calling sylvia out there a liar. oh, no, no, sylvia wouldn't tell you shit. wrong. one compliment about her hair, and she told me you gave louis the bad news an hour ago. see you around, robert. harvey, one more thing. you do still owe me that favor. what kind of math are you doing? the kind of math that says jessica pearson hiring louis litt back adds up to shady. if that's all you've got, you can collect your favor when the clock strikes kiss my ass, because partners leave firms and come back all the time. maybe, but they don't come back with their name on the wall. ah, i'm guessing he wasn't supposed to tell me that. but he did, and louis litt is not name partner material, which means he must have something on you. so unless you want me going around town flapping my big mouth that something isn't right in your kitchen, you're gonna make good on that favor. sylvia didn't slip up at all, did she? no, she didn't. you have your girl friday i have mine. but you can still tell her how nice her hair looks on the way out. i'll be in touch. oh, you're tapping out already? i thought you'd have a lot more backbone than that. i'm not tapping out. i finished all of the work. which i expected to be done an hour ago. come on, louis, you didn't expect it to be done at all. just like you didn't expect this. what the hell is that? it's a gift certificate. what, are you trying to bribe me now? it's not a bribe, it's a reminder. look, the gift certificate is from peter's steak house, the place that you and i saved together. and after we saved it, you told me that we had something in common. yeah, i don't give a shit. yes, you do, because what we had in common was a love of the law. you told me that when you asked me to be your associate, louis, and i am still the same person. and if i found out a woman i had something in common with was actually a man, i wouldn't keep seeing her. okay, what i did is not at all the same thing. no, it's worse. you say you love the law so much, but every single case you've ever touched is tainted. so you get exposed, peter's gets bulldozed. it wouldn't even be there to get bulldozed if you and i hadn't worked together. all right, genius. you want to work together? you love the law so much? you're gonna memorize every case that i've ever done. louis. no, get to work, and use that magnificent memory of yours for something more than bullshitting your way through life. we have a problem. unless it's urgent, i don't have the time. louis is telling people. what people? for starters, robert zane. why the hell is louis even talking to robert zane? i asked him to hire louis after we took back versalife. and you didn't think to tell me that after last night? i was handling it. from what i can tell, you handled it like shit. so this is my fault? well, it sure as hell isn't mine. you know what, jessica, i'm not the one who wanted to fire louis, and i'm not the one who wanted to deny him clients. i did that because of his performance as an attorney. you antagonized him for years for your own pleasure. tell yourself whatever you want. you handed out your share of abuse. tell yourself whatever you want. you're the one who hired a fraud and gave louis leverage. and i told you louis would get worse, and you said i had to take it. well, i don't care whose fault it is, he is getting worse, and i'm not gonna take it. oh, yes, you are. you're going to take it, and you're gonna do it with a smile on your face until i say otherwise. and what the hell are you gonna do? i'm going to clean up this mess once and for all. what do you mean, you don't have diamond encrusted business cards? fine, what about the embossed ivory? okay, great, well, how much would , of those run me? money's no object. what, are you crazy? i'm not paying that much. unless it comes with a reach around. which, by the way, i'm still not paying that much. elite printing, my ass. i give you one simple instruction. to keep your mouth shut. and you couldn't even do that. um, okay, did you make an appointment with norma? what? to see me. did you check with my secretary, norma? cut the shit, louis. i'm not in the mood. well, get in the mood, because i hold all the cards. and those cards are getting you your name on the wall, but you need to keep this to yourself. why? so you can figure out a way to screw me? i gave you my word. well, no disrespect, jessica, but your word means shit. so if you want me to stop telling people, you better start telling people yourself. i told you, in good time. and i just told you i don't give a shit. so i suggest you call a meeting with the senior partners. those meetings are on thursdays. well, consider today thursday. i told you, i have yet to figure out how to sell it. you want to sell it? i'll tell you how to sell it. you and harvey do it together, you do it like you mean it. and you do it now. got it? good. i'm sure you've all heard rumors about why we called this meeting, but that's because it's hard to keep good news quiet. we'll be making this official later this week but we're here to announce our newest name partner, louis litt. thank you, jessica. harvey. some of you may be wondering how this happened. there's a simple explanation, and all it requires is for me to admit something. i made a mistake. i never should have accepted louis's resignation, because not only is he a billing machine and a damn good attorney, he has personally gotten me out of more than one jam, and there's no one i'd rather have my name next to than my friend louis litt. thank you, harvey. even though it's not official, i already feel like my name's been up there as long as yours. and i definitely feel like it's gonna be up there for a long, long time. a lot of good that did. leave it to louis to take his big moment like a dick. harvey, calm down. calm down? i just did exactly what he wanted, and he acted like a dick, and he's not gonna stop. he's not gonna stop because you didn't do what he wanted. jessica, i just got up there and kissed his ass in front of the entire partnership and pretended to like it. exactly. pretended. oh, you want me to actually like it? i want you to make him feel accepted. jessica. harvey, what louis wants is to be accepted. and like it or not, the person he wants that from the most is you. so you're gonna go to him, you're gonna make nice, and that's how we're gonna put all of this to bed. you want to tell me what the hell that was? if you'll excuse me, i'm gonna let jessica handle this conversation. i have to go kill myself. jeff, i can't do this right now. should i make an appointment? because the partners may have bought that fairy tale about louis's triumphant return, but they don't know what i know. what exactly is that? that louis committed a crime, and then he resigned five seconds before you were about to fire him. and now he's not only back, he's name partner. i reconsidered, which, as managing partner, i am entitled to do. and as someone with a brain, i'm entitled to come to the conclusion that louis has something on you. jeff, you said you didn't want me to lie to you anymore, and i'm trying like hell not to. and that's the same thing as lying to me. no, it's not. oh, you are one hell of a lawyer. so are you, which is why you're here. so i'll come clean. i can't tell you the truth about this, and that's as honest as i can be with you right now. can you handle that? i can handle it for now. but i won't handle it forever. louis, what are you doing here? i noticed you haven't congratulated me yet, so i wanted to give you a chance to make up for it. right, congratulations. we're all so happy for you. is that what you wanted? seemed a little disingenuous. then let me be clear. i don't mean a word of it. you really want to talk that way to a new name partner? i'm talking to you that way because you threatened to throw the man that i love in jail to become that name partner. so, you know what, louis, i'm sorry that i didn't bake you a cake. that's too bad. you didn't do anything for me, but i got something for you. doc review. filings to be done in triplicate. paralegal work, since you like doing it so much. you know i don't like doing it at all. you helped your boyfriend with his work. you didn't think i'd figure that out? you know what? i don't care. you have no authority over me. i'm harvey's associate. yeah, but i run the associates. therefore, i run you. i know what you're doing. but do you know what you're doing? not only do you live with a fraud, you're just like him. pretending to be a lawyer when you're not. i'm not pretending to be anything. i am in law school. are you really gonna make it through? you could barely handle the lsats. you couldn't get into harvard. as a matter of fact, your boyfriend may be a fraud, but he's a better lawyer than you'll ever be. you have no idea what kind of lawyer i'm gonna be. don't i? you learned from the best liars around, rachel harvey, mike, your father. yeah, i know exactly the kind of lawyer you're gonna be. but until that day, this kind of work is all you're good for. so you like marinated meat? oh, yum. okay, wait, but which one do you make? kansas city or memphis style? oh, hell, when it comes to ribs, i make 'em every which way i can. i am now officially starving. harvey. please have a seat. don't let my law firm get in the way of your coffee klatch. oh, now, now, don't blame donna here. i told her you and i had some unfinished business. already? what, did you pick something out of your generic favor file? i've never done anything generic in my life. this favor is tailor made for you. it's very specific and very personal. we're in a little dispute with another firm. i need you to get them to back off of it. why can't you do it yourself? 'cause i don't know the lawyer on the other side. you do. good luck. what the hell is he talking about? it's scottie. aw, shit. i know. scottie doesn't do favors like this, and i don't have any leverage on her. yeah, you do. you're just not gonna like using it. hey, there you are. look, i just finished memorizing all of louis's cases, and i had an idea i wanted to run by. rachel, what happened? nothing happened. what did louis do? it's nothing. he found out that i helped you, and now he's giving me paralegal work, and i was a little upset, but now i'm okay. you weren't just a little upset. you were crying, and a little paralegal work wouldn't do that. it is not important. and you know what? i had it coming. you had it coming? what are you. rachel, what did he do? mike, i was the one that told you to make up with him. rachel. i helped you with the work. what did he do? and you know what? i lied to him as much as you did. what did he do? it's not what he did, it's what he said. what did he say? mike, i'm a big girl, and i can take care of louis. this isn't about you, this is about me and him, and i'm gonna make him remember that. you piece of shit. you said this was between me and you. it is between me and you. no, it stopped being between me and you the second you went to rachel. you put her between us the second you went to her to help you. god, are you insane? rachel has never been anything but kind to you. i can't even count the amount of times that she defended you. and now, she tries to help me just a little bit, and you rip her to pieces. no, that's not the help i'm talking about, fraud. then what the hell are you talking about? you went to her to help you lie to me about who you are, and like the good little lackey that she is, she came to me and lied to my face. she did it to protect me, louis. well, good for you, but when i found out about it, i felt like shit for the th time. so i just went to her and did the same thing. you know, louis, i've just been memorizing all of your old arguments. i was actually gonna try and come in here and use one of them to change your mind about me. it won't work. oh, i know. because while i am the same person that i was before, you're not. you're right. i'm not the same person. i used to be a man of my word, but you people taught me that doesn't mean a thing. so when i told you it was between me and you, i lied. i found your weak spot, and you know what i'm gonna do? i'm gonna keep hammering on her until you break. jessica. please, if it can wait, i've had a long day, and i need to go home. too bad. you're staying here and drafting louis litt's new partnership agreement. so now you're piling on too now? i'm not piling on. i am giving you this because it's non billable work and the only reason it exists is because of you. this again? excuse me? you heard me. i've seen this movie before. and the reason it keeps rerunning is because every time i think i'm done with you, you and your dirty little secret rear your ugly heads. you know what, jessica? i have had it up to here with you saying that this is my dirty little secret. you could have fired me when you found out, and you didn't. no, you decided to keep me around because you were more concerned with beating daniel hardman and keeping your power. and then you kept me around because you didn't want to lose harvey. and then you wanted to use my secret to beat harvey, and then again and again and again. so please, jessica, why don't you tell me, when the hell does this become your dirty little secret? this seat taken? hi. hey. since your message was so cryptic, i'm assuming this is about business. i need a favor. hey, scottie. how are you? how have you been since you left? i heard that you took some time off. where did you land? i need you to settle your case against robert zane. and why would i do that? because i owe him one. harvey, i'm just getting back on my feet at a new firm. this case is winnable. the firm knows that it is because i told them it is. i settle, i look like shit. i know that, but you came to me once to take it easy on you with folsom foods. because you said if i was ever in trouble personally. i am in trouble personally. what the hell is personal about robert zane? you don't do this for me, zane's going to put it together about mike ross. scottie. you selfish son of a bitch. you said you told me that because you didn't want to keep lying to the people you love. i didn't want to. and now you come to me trading on the fact that i know to get you out of a jam for doing something stupid and selfish that drove a wedge between us before we ever even had a chance. i told you the truth. after it was too late. scottie. i loved you. i loved you, and you let some stupid secret that i would never tell anyone come between us because you couldn't trust me with it. you're right, scottie. i don't have a leg to stand on. but if you don't do this for me, i am in trouble. i'm going to recommend we settle with robert zane. thank you. but to be clear, you get to ask me this once. and i never want to hear the name mike ross again. scottie. once. you wanted it to be official. there it is, louis. it's official. so that's it? people are just gonna walk in here tomorrow morning like it's any other day and see it or maybe not see it? what were you expecting? a ceremony and a brass band? we don't do that. well, i'm name partner, and i say we do now. excuse me? you heard me. i want pomp and circumstance in the form of an unveiling. i'm going home, louis. i'm not spending the rest of the night emailing invitations to an unveiling. you're going home? well, then i'll send them out myself. because tomorrow. this is happening. p.m. sharp. i have a meeting at . then reschedule it. you don't want me to reschedule. what you want is to know you've earned that. i have earned it, but i want you to know it. okay, here it is. you got your name up there by finding leverage and using it to strong arm me into doing something that i never would have done. see, i knew you. let me finish. it was a stone cold move, and it's exactly what harvey would have done. now, if that doesn't tell you that you've earned it, then i don't know what will. you still want me to reschedule my meeting? yes, i do. fine. i'll be there. you and harvey. of course, louis. we're your partners. jesus, you look like shit. what's going on? between drafting louis's partnership agreement for jessica and louis's never ending onslaught, i didn't get any sleep. well, splash some water on your face, 'cause we have to go to his debutante ball and look like we give a shit. no. i'm not going. what do you mean you're not going? now is not the time to poke the bear. it's too late. the bear is an asshole, and he's not just taking it out on me anymore. he's taking it out on rachel. what? yeah, he made it clear that he found the weak spot that's going to get to me, and he's gonna keep pressing it and pressing it until i can't take it anymore. mike, you are not ringing that bell. you're damn right i'm not ringing that bell. but if i have to go raise a glass to that son of a bitch, i'm gonna end up smashing it over his head. come with me. what are you going to do? enough is enough. harvey. you're just in time. jessica's on her way down with the partnership agreement. you here to be my witness? he's here to keep me from ripping your face off. oh, i see. now that big brother's here. okay, that's enough. louis, you got everything you wanted, and you are done taking it out on him, because no matter what you do, i'm not letting him quit. then i'll just fire him. you can't. i can, and i will, because jessica would rather he be fired than you all go to jail. no one's going to jail. see? she knows what's what. i sign the agreement, he's done, and then i bring katrina back as my associate. and that's not going to happen. what are you talking about? louis, i'm afraid you've made your last dictate to me as name partner. i'm not gonna let you take this away from me. i'm not taking anything away from you. you are still name partner. right after you sign this. i added a little something extra after you finished drafting it. this says i'm co conspirator to hiring a fraud. you are. you became one the second you used him to get your name on the door. i know i'm not a real lawyer, but that sounds like he is to me. i am a real lawyer. he is. i'm not signing it. louis, here's the thing. i told you not to tell anybody about this, and then you went and you shouted it to robert zane, and then you made me tell the partners. and the capper is, there are about a hundred people waiting to greet you after the unveiling you arranged, which won't happen if you don't sign that. i could still go to the police. yeah, you could, but you won't. 'cause you used that little secret to get where you are right now. it was the only bullet in your chamber, and i am taking your gun away. you set me up. you set yourself up, just like you did with charles forstman. and what i learned from him was, once you get something that you want, you will do whatever it takes to keep it. so why don't you go ahead and sign so we can get out to your goddamn party. you know, it's funny. we've never had a ceremony when we've changed names before, but louis litt had the audacity to convene us all here today. and as it turns out, his first decision as name partner is brilliant, because a ceremony like this gives us a chance to reevaluate where we've been and where we're going. perhaps you had a disagreement with a colleague, or there's some other issue that's been on your mind. the point is, with a new name comes a new beginning. for me, i'm hoping we can see this as a chance to wipe the slate clean. with that said, here's to our newest name partner, louis litt. nice speech. let's hope it takes. it's got a better chance of taking now that you made him sign the agreement. that it does. speaking of which, when exactly did you know you were gonna do that? oh, um, about seconds after donna told me he knew. and you didn't feel the need to bring me in on that plan? i felt the exact opposite. what are you talking about? harvey, louis wanted to see you suffer. if i had told you, you would have had to fake it, and you're a shitty actor. excuse me, but i can act. no, everybody thinks they can act, harvey. the fact of the matter is, well, you're just a pretty face. oh, you think i'm pretty? pretty stupid. i can't believe it's actually up there. this firm is changing names more than prince. who? you're kidding, right? purple rain. raspberry beret. i'm kidding. i almost had to reevaluate our entire relationship. mm hmm, after you were gonna go and beat louis up for me? i doubt that. mike, thank you. it just seemed right. after all, you stood up to louis for me. mm hmm, and i almost got pummeled for it. that took guts. and that's why i love you. i love you too. i wanted to tell you that you were right. i started this whole thing by hiring mike. it's my fault. thank you. but i've been on board long enough, and it's time i accepted the fact that it's my secret too. so where do we go from here? we fight like hell to protect it. no cake? what are you doing here, jessica? i know you're tired of waiting for an explanation, so i'm here to give you one. you've given me explanations before. i want the truth. are you ready for the truth? because it's not pretty. there's only one way to find out. it seems like forever ago, but it wasn't that long ago at all. daniel hardman embezzled money from the firm, and i covered it up. now, make no mistake, i found about it, i confronted him, and i eventually made him pay it all back. but i did cover it up. from the partners, from the police, from everyone. i even adjusted our books to hide the crime. and being a bloodhound about these things, louis found out and used it as leverage to come back. as name partner. as name partner. why couldn't you trust me with that before? because i didn't know how you'd react, and i didn't want to risk losing everything i had. jessica, your secret is safe with me. you're late. but i come bearing gifts. huh. that doesn't look like cannoli. it's better than cannoli, dad. it's the r sum of your new associate. if this is harvey's way of trying to make up for the fact that i didn't hire louis. this isn't from harvey. it's from me. and you're going to do this for me, and i am not going to owe you a thing. this is what they're teaching you at columbia? because that's not how favors work. i know how favors work. you do this, and then you want something from me someday. but by then you're going to understand that right now i'm the one doing you a favor, because katrina bennett is an amazing lawyer. i was wrong about you. you're not like your mother. you're like your father. come on. oh, that's good. that was a good one. that was a good one. sounds just like me, baby girl. i had you fooled, huh? you did. now let me show you how a lawyer cooks. what do you want? i just thought you'd want this. the associates saved it for you. no, they didn't. you saved it for me because you want to pretend to be my friend again. louis, didn't you hear jessica's speech? this is our chance wipe the slate clean. i did hear her speech, and i know that she sent you here to say that to me. no one sent me here. i'm here because i want to be here. you see, that's sweet. but how can i ever believe a word you say? i want to know if you ever thought once to tell me the truth about mike. no, i didn't. of course you didn't. because we're not friends. you're wrong. we are friends, but my professional loyalty to harvey comes above that, which is why i never told anyone. jessica, rachel, anyone. so put yourself in my position and ask yourself, what you would have done? i want you to tell me something else. yes. anything. you ever sleep with harvey? wait. what? it's not a professional question. it's a personal question. can you put our so called friendship high enough to answer that one honestly? louis. because it's the only thing i can think of to know if i can even begin to trust you again. once. that's my way of wiping the slate clean. you can accept it or not