 you never let me tell you what the money was for. you didn't listen to me when i told you i don't care. well, do you care that after mike grilled me, i was so impressed with him that i wonder why i'd forgotten him? but i couldn't find any record of him ever being in my class. just like they're not gonna find any record of you accepting a bribe from a student. jessica, your secret is safe with me. i told him you found out that i covered up daniel hardman's embezzlement. and now you want me to protect another one of your secrets. it's the same secret, louis, and you have just as much invested in it as i do. you want me to kiss the ring, louis, after what you did? you're damn right i do, because i don't care how it got up there. my name is on that wall whether you like it or not. hey. hey. what do you think of this tie? i think. i want to tie you up with it. really? and what brought that on? okay, well, then let's make that happen. wait. is this to do things to me or just to get control of the remote? why can't it be both? rachel, if you think i'm gonna let you watch game of thrones while sexually dominating me, then you are absolutely right. seriously, what's got you feeling so good? oh, it just feels like such a weight off now that louis doesn't. despise me? mm hmm. ah, you know what else would feel like a weight off? oh. no. no, no, no. nobody ever calls the landline except my parents. what if something's wrong? it's fine. mike. okay, okay, okay. hello. yeah, this is him. yeah, of course i can come meet you. can i ask what this is. hello? who was it? professor gerard. he wants me to go meet him. did he say what it was about? no, he hung up. when does he want you to meet him? right now. professor gerard. thanks for coming. i wouldn't have bothered you if it wasn't important. it's not a problem. what can i help you with? it's not me. a former employee at liberty rail reached out to me. he claims he was fired because he knows the real reason for the crash. and what was the real reason? he wouldn't tell me. well, what did he tell you? enough for me to know it would be unethical if somebody didn't look into this. but you can't, so you want me to get harvey to. well, you convinced him to look into my case when he didn't want to, didn't you? this is different. we don't take cases like this. maybe, but i believe a man who can convince harvey to hire someone who never went to law school could convince him to make an exception for this. what? he didn't tell you i know. no, he didn't. well, i do. but what i'm asking you to do and me knowing have nothing to do with each other. i appreciate that. does that mean that you're gonna tell him to take the case? i have a better idea. got a second? of course. what do you need? i'd like you to sign off on my vacation request. paris. i've never heard you talk about paris. no, but i have heard you talk about it, which is why i'm taking you. are you asking me to go to paris with you? i believe i just did. jeff, do you have any idea how much is on my plate right now? actually, i do, all of which harvey has agreed to cover. you went to harvey with this. well, i would have come to you first, but then it really wouldn't be a surprise. i'll think about it. take all the time you need. but in the meantime, i'll be thinking about who else around here i can take. really? well, you're awfully sure of yourself. you think i haven't seen the way norma looks at me? calls me the black stallion. norma. taking a case. what kind of case? what does it matter? because you wouldn't be announcing it like that if there wasn't something wrong. it's a case that came from professor gerard. what? a man who used to work at liberty rail says the real cause of the crash was covered up. then refer him to a firm that takes whistle blower cases, because we don't. yeah, i'm not gonna do that. then don't, but there's a reason lawyers who take whistle blower cases don't work here, and it's because corporations don't appreciate shakedown artists. and what if this isn't a shakedown? and how do you know it isn't? what i know is that innocent people died. mothers and fathers and sons and daughters. and if somebody's covering up why that happened and i can stop it, then i'm going to. and i said you're not. well, but you also said that professor gerard didn't know my secret. harvey, i know, i know he'll never tell anyone, but someday, someone's gonna find out who will, and i'll be done. mike, he's not. harvey, i got into this whole thing so that i could try to help people, and i don't know how much time i have left, so please, let me try and help these people. then you better make damn sure this whistle blower isn't full of sh. see the money, wanna stay for your meal get another piece of pie for your wife everybody wanna know how it feel everybody wanna see what it's like i'll even eat a bean pie, i don't mind me and missy is so busy, busy making money all right all step back, i'm 'bout to dance suits x derailed original air date on february , the greenback boogie sync, corrected by elderman elder man. bonjour, madame. oh, i'm so glad you started with that french bullshit, because that's what i want to talk to you about. i know. never thought i'd have someone ask my permission to take you to paris. you know damn well that's not what jeff did. jessica, what exactly do you want to talk about? i want to know why you cleared my schedule. because jeff asked me to, and i can't remember the last time you took a vacation. when's the last time you took a vacation? i'm not the one in a serious relationship. oh, so you're playing matchmaker for me now? oh, i'm not playing anything, and you were the one who said you had to choose between hiring him and continuing to see him. and then i changed my mind. and i don't want you to make the same mistake i did. what are you talking about? i should have taken some time with scottie. jeff and i are not you and scottie. jessica, take a vacation. don't take a vacation. the man came in here, asking me for help because he wants to go away with you, and i said yes because i'm not gonna be the reason he can't. pearson specter, how may i direct your call? pearson specter, how may i direct your call? louis, do you have a minute? no, i don't. okay. what are you doing? pearson specter, how may i direct your call? pearson specter, how may i direct your call? you hear. pearson specter, how may i direct your call? hello? pearson specter. you hear that? where's the litt? every call is like a slap in the face. louis, it's standard practice for a law firm to shorten their name on the phone. so blatant disrespect is standard practice now? it's not disrespect. it's just. you're telling me that your father doesn't have them answer the phone, rand, kaldore, zane ? actually, no, he doesn't, and i think you'd agree that people respect my father. unless you want to go back to telling me that he's a shady lawyer. come on, rachel, that was when i was mad at you. which is actually why i wanted to come and talk to you. i want to thank you for forgiving mike. it. it means a lot to me. now, can you stop obsessing over the phone long enough to hear that? i'm sorry, rachel, but i can't, and now i have to go rip that receptionist a new ass. louis, if one of your first acts as name partner is to rip the receptionist to shreds, you'll regret that for the rest of your life. just let it go. let it go. things will run their course. you know what, rachel? you're right. and by the way, i'm glad that we're friends again. pearson specter. harvey, what are you doing at this afternoon? why? i have some news, and i don't want you to overreact. what is it? jeffrey bender wants to meet with you. he heard we're taking a whistle blower case, and he wants us to drop it. relax, i'll take care of jeffrey bender. wait a second, you're not gonna try to cut mike's legs out from under him before he even gets started? what's the point? he'd just bother me until i agreed not to anyway. i can't believe it. you have no idea what to say. what's the date today? i want to write this down. you know what? it's the seventh of kiss my ass, and tomorrow is the eighth of set your own goddamn meetings. is that the mayan calendar? nope, that's the donna calendar. i got you. for the record, i got you. all right, take me through it one more time. it's simple. there are axles on all the cars in all the trains, and those axles have sensors to make sure they don't overheat. so you're saying that the train crashed because the heat sensors failed. i'm saying that all the heat sensors on the entire fleet were faulty, and they knew about it. then why didn't you come forward with this before? you mean before they fired me for coming forward with it? which brings me to my next question. you've had four different jobs in the last six years. what are you getting at? i want to know why. i move around. it's not uncommon in my business. move around or keep failing? i got fired for blowing the whistle, not for messing up on the job. that's not what your last performance review says. i don't give a shit what it says. they used that as an excuse to fire me, and my reviews before i came forward passed with flying colors. i'm a solid worker. how the hell do you think i got this? i know your reviews are stellar. what i need to know is if there's anything out there that we don't have, because they are gonna come at us any way they can, and when they do, it's not gonna be about heat sensors. it's gonna be about you. yeah, i don't care if i'm the worst guy in the world. i know i'm not the only guy in that company that knows those sensors are faulty. what are you talking about? what do you mean, there's a report? done after the crash that showed a defective part was the real cause, not engineer error. says the whistle blower. says these. that's a memo ordering the report and another email acknowledging its existence. we got 'em. we do. set a meeting. let them do the talking, then drop the hammer, and stick a settlement down their throat before they know what hit them. i appreciate the advice, harvey, but this time i'm going in with the hammer in my hand, and i am coming out swinging. okay, big talker, how much you asking for? million. are you kidding me? they'll pay ten times that without even trying. not when i tell them they're gonna have to admit what they did. are you nuts? no, i am not. we are not sealing this settlement, and before you say another word, this is my case. i don't care whose case it is. they're never going to admit what they did. pick a higher number and let them seal it. harvey, you told me to prove this wasn't a shakedown. now you want me to take money to cover things up? you know what that is? a shakedown! a shakedown is when your case has no merit. this is the way things work. not to mention, if we quietly settle, we don't have to worry about scaring away our clients. that's why it's the way things work. harvey, people died in this crash! and they're not coming back, no matter what liberty rail admits. you are such a cold, heartless son of a bitch. and this isn't about your parents, so back them into whatever corner you want, but when they refuse to admit what they did, you are not going to trial. stay out of my case. something smells delicious. i'm making us dinner, but it won't be ready for a while. good, that means we have time to go over my proposed itinerary. i don't recall saying yes. i thought that we would start with a private tour of the rodin. oh, the rodin. god, i must have visited that sculpture garden a dozen times. then i'm so glad that i arranged for us to have a picnic while we're there, and during that picnic, we can reminisce about the week before, where we danced the night away in the latin quarter. we did? mm, or we'll talk about how we'll end the trip in the loire valley, where we will sip wine along the seine. jeff, this trip is perfect. how did you know? i know you've always loved paris, so i started there. and then i called your sister. you did that for me? i did. so what do you say? i say, if you knew what i was cooking, you'd already know my answer. looks french. mm hmm. so you let me go through all that even though you knew you were gonna say yes the entire time? mm hmm. aren't you glad i did? yes, jessica. yes, i am. donna, what are you doing here? i'm here because i can't take it anymore. what? this place has no life, and i can't take it anymore. and that's gonna add life? if i gave you something too needy, it would intimidate you, and you would let it die. you expect me to believe that's why you're really here? of course not. i'm here to stop you from doing what you're gonna do in an hour crash mike's meeting. donna, i can't have him risking our other business. it was one client, and you covered it. and if he drags this to trial, it will be every client. you don't know that. yes, i do. then trust him to accept that on his own. donna. harvey, when are you gonna let him be his own man? his own man? he's out of control. he's identifying these people with his parents. and you're out of control because you can't separate yourself from him. okay, you need to stay out of it. and i will, but you said you made a mistake not trusting mike with gillis industries. i'm telling you, don't make that mistake again. pearson specter, how may i direct your call? uh. rand, kaldore, zane. son of a bitch! hello, liar. excuse me? rand, kaldore, zane. you know what that is? that's how they answer the phone at rand, kaldore, zane. louis, i'm sorry. oh, save your sorrys. do you know the receptionist at the front desk? yes, her name is elise. good, you can use her name when you fire her. i don't have the authority to fire people, but i did just talk to her. you did? mm hmm. to set her straight. that's good. no, not good. she came to see me. she said that you've been harassing her. what happened? she said that you called and hung up on her over times. what? how did she even know it was me? because you called from your office. well, it wasn't harassment because it wasn't sexual. well, she also said that you were leering at her when you stepped off the elevator. i wasn't leering! i was mad about how she answered the phone. louis, it doesn't matter why you did it. she felt violated. well, you know what, you tell her it's not like that, and then you violate her ass out the door. louis, is this really the kind of name partner you want to be? no, i want to be the kind of name partner that has his name said on the goddamn phone. okay, well, in order to fire her without getting sued for harassment, you'd have to fire the entire support staff, and you and i both know that that's never going to happen. we are not firing all of our support staff. well, it's easy for you to say, being that your name is first. what are you talking. jessica, i am talking about respect. r e s p e c t, find out what it means to me. but i guess i'll just find my own way to be treated how i deserve. i know i'm gonna regret asking this. louis, tell me specifically what it is you're talking about. they are answering the phones, pearson specter, not pearson specter litt. louis. you don't believe me? check it yourself. i'm not harassing our support staff. it's not harassment, god damn it! louis! jessica, it's like they've been specifically instructed to leave my name off. now you're just being paranoid. i am not paranoid. they're in lockstep. i'm telling you, someone paid them off. louis, that's insane, but if you want them to say your name, i will get them to say your name. jessica, what can i do for you? you can explain to me why you paid our reception staff not to say louis' name when they answer the phone. who says i did that? they do. god damn it. i paid them good money to keep louis from finding out for at least a month. he hasn't found out. it wasn't him who got them to crack, it was me. even still, i'm asking for a refund. jeff, i'm serious about this. i know you're pissed about how he got his name on the door, but i need you to bury the hatchet. well, i'm not gonna do that. why not? because every single time i see his rat face, i think about him blackmailing you, and it makes me want to walk over to him and rip his arms off his body, and that little phone prank was just my way of keeping myself from doing something like that. i understand, and i do appreciate it, but i'm not asking you to do it for him. i'm asking you to do it for me. mr. ross. all i can say about your filing is that i think you might have a career writing fiction. and if you don't hand over that report we're requesting, you're gonna have a career behind bars. you're not here for that report. you're here to strong arm my client into a big, fat check. i'm sorry to be the one to tell you this, but a big, fat check isn't gonna get you out of this. is that a fact? sure as hell is, because we both know that report says you're responsible for this accident, and we're not settling anything without you admitting it. and we're not admitting something we didn't do. what the hell is this? well, you wanted the report. here it is. your client wasn't lying about its existence. he was just lying about everything else. we ran repeated tests on our heat sensors, and they passed every one. this is bullshit. the only thing that's bullshit is joe henderson. he doesn't care about the accident. all he's trying to do is shake us down, exactly like he did at his last four jobs. what the hell is that? his last four lawsuits. did you think we wouldn't find out about them just because the records were sealed? mr. ross, your client's been playing the whistle blower lottery for years. he's never won before. he's not going to win today. you son of a bitch, you tried to blow the whistle at every job you've ever had, and now they know it! keep your voice down. you. no, i'll keep my voice down when you stop bullshit ing me. those claims were supposed to be sealed. i don't care what they were supposed to be. they found them, and you were supposed to tell me about them. and what would you have done if i did? i would've said what they said, that you don't give a shit about what they did! you're just looking to get rich. you think i would've risked my job and everything that i have for nothing? excuse me? i said, i don't see you working out of the goodness of your heart in your , suit. you have no idea who i am or why i do things. and i told you, you don't have to be concerned about my history because what i'm telling you is true. not according to this. that's the report that you said gave us all the leverage and they say proves them innocent. that report is bullshit, because i'm telling you, those sensors didn't work, and that was the cause of that accident. well, i might have a leg to stand on if you had any credibility at all. how the hell am i supposed to get a jury to believe you when i'm not even sure i do? what are you doing here? i'm here to tell you to call the front desk. oh, let me guess. jessica told you they won't say my name and you thought it was hilarious. you're right, i did. why don't you get the hell out of my office and go laugh somewhere else? oh, you want to hit me now? yeah, well, why don't you go ask mike ross about my headlock? 'cause it's a goddamn vice. pearson specter litt, how may i direct your call? it was you. yes, it was me, but i fixed it, so. you can stop worrying if everybody at the firm respects you, because they do. everyone except you. no, louis, including me. listen, i may not like how you got your name on the wall, but that doesn't mean it shouldn't be up there. congratulations, louis. thanks, jeff. hey, maybe we can even get drinks this week. name partner buys. deal. done. you can leave the coffee, but i'm not getting up. mike, you've been working for seven hours straight. you need a break. i've been working for seven hours because if i tell harvey what's going on before i have a fix, he is gonna pull the plug. well, then maybe the plug needs to be pulled. rachel, just because joe henderson is a bullshit plaintiff doesn't mean they didn't cover things up. it doesn't mean that they did. okay, fine. why would he ask for that report if he knew it would hurt our case? i don't know. i don't know either, which is why i need more time. well, then you need to convince harvey to let you keep going, because if you don't and he finds out. he is not gonna find out. mike, he's not gonna find out from me, but if i've learned one thing in the last six months of working here, it's that if he finds out from somebody else, you're gonna regret it. you come here to tell me you're taking that vacation? i came by to ask when mike ross started taking whistle blower cases. jessica. i want you to put the brakes on him before this gets out of control. well, i'm not gonna do that. harvey. jessica, it's one case. he asked me to trust him, and i'm gonna do it, and if you're ever gonna be able to enjoy a vacation, you're gonna have to trust me. all right. good night. bon voyage. you do know that doesn't mean good night. of course i do. do you know how to say good night in french? what, do you think i'm some kind of neanderthal? you don't know one word of french, do you? m nage trois. you're an idiot. m nage quatre. m nage cinq. can i come in? what's going on? we have a problem. i'm listening. liberty rail's report directly contradicts our claim. that's a big damn problem. i believe my client, harvey. based on what, your gut? no, i found the guy who wrote the report. he's on indefinite leave in australia, where we can't subpoena him. so it's our word against theirs. which is why i'm here. joe henderson made four other claims in the last six years. you're shit ing me. harvey. that's it. i'm pulling the plug. i knew it. i knew you would bail on me the second this thing hit the smallest bump. bail on you? i backed you because you told me you had a case. i do have a case. i told you they got to this guy. and you got no proof of that. and if this were your case, you would be begging me for help to get it. it's not my case. it's yours. and now you're asking a jury to believe these guys fabricated a report based on the word of a career whistle blower. no, i'm asking you to believe it. it doesn't matter what i believe. this guy is a goddamn shakedown artist, and i'm pulling the plug. i don't care what he is. i'm not a goddamn shakedown artist! mike. harvey, you told me that those people weren't my parents, but they are somebody's parents. please. you got hours. you know it's against the law to litter, don't you? what do you want, donna? i know you went to see harvey. you know that he wants me to fail. that's not true. i don't have anything, and he only gave me a day. and if he wanted you to fail, he wouldn't have given you another second. you know he thinks this is about my parents, right? is it? maybe it is, but what these people did is a million times worse because they knew it could happen. wait a second. they knew this could happen, and they didn't fix it before? yeah, donna, and then they. they rolled the dice. well, what about now? are those trains still messed up? because that would make them monsters. they are monsters, but that would also make them idiots, and they're not idiots. well, what are you talking about? well, they must have fixed the sensors by now otherwise if it happened again, they'd all go to jail. well, if they fixed the sensors, then there has to be a paper trail. of course there is. then all you have to do is get it. what do you think i've been trying to figure out all night? what's to figure out? subpoena it. yeah, there's only one problem. harvey only gave me hours. but now that you've come up with this, maybe harvey will change his mind. donna, i have a theory that i can't prove and an opposition that's shown they're willing to alter evidence. he's not gonna change his mind, and you know it. there's got to be another way. donna, look, i appreciate what you're doing, but unless you have this other way in your pocket, please, just leave me alone and let me try and think this thing through. no! i don't care what he says. it's an active goddamn investigation, and i'm not gonna stand around. you can't talk on that here. hang on a second, charlie. i'm sorry, we got off on the wrong foot. is your name danielle? that's what it says on the plate, isn't it? well, danielle, i'm here to pick up the documents i ordered an hour ago, and if you don't give them to me in the next seconds, today's gonna be your last day. you didn't talk to me. i said hold on, damn it. look, i don't have time to play who spoke to who. i am up from dc because, as it is, these documents weren't sent when they were promised. i'm sorry. what is it you need again? oh, jesus christ. all the maintenance work orders from the past six months. i can't let you have that without authorization. well, then by all means, let's call your supervisor, and we can tell him how you'd rather play farmville than cooperate with me. who did you say you're with again? have you heard of the national transportation safety board? they'll give you what you need in the back. what did you do? i didn't do anything. what did you do? don't give me that. this makes my entire case, but i can't use it if i don't know where it came from. oh, that looks like it came from liberty rail. oh, oh, yeah, it just happened to walk itself over from their secure facility. well, it's possible that somebody went over there and released it from their secure facility. donna, if i go to harvey with this and tell him what i know happened, he. you don't know. you think. don't lawyer me. he'll never let me use it. well, then don't tell him what you think happened, because if you do, he'll make you drop the case. okay, right now, i don't care about the case. i care about you. mike, i didn't steal anything. i talked my way in, and that's what happened. did you tell them this was discovery for a case against them? no. then it's not admissible in court. well, then you have to figure out a way to use it not in court, but don't ask me for my help on that. i have done enough. hey. heard you wanted to see me. i take it you patched things up with louis litt. how do you know? oh, he wanted to know if you were a sports bar guy or a wine bar guy. did you tell him i'm more of a strip club kind of guy? you really want to go to a strip club with louis litt? i don't really want to go to a strip club with anyone, but i do have a meeting in minutes, and it's minutes away. oh, i just wanted to tell you that i appreciate you patching things up with him. there's no need to thank me. i would do anything for the woman that i love. even get a drink with louis litt. you here to talk about anderton software? because your hour liberty rail pass is up. then i guess it's a good thing that just came in the mail for me. what is it? maintenance records showing they replaced the heat sensors on all of their trains within six weeks after the derailment. now, why would they do that if they never failed a safety test? they wouldn't. which means joe henderson was telling the truth. i can think of three different ways they'll explain this away. not if we can get them on record before they know we have it. and why don't they know we have it? the same way i didn't know they got joe henderson's sealed records. which means you did something sketchy. harvey, do you want to spend all night asking me exactly what i did or did not do, or do you want to help me right a wrong? donna? set a deposition with liberty rail, and tell them this time it won't just be mike. i'm on it. who the hell is that? that's the ceo of liberty rail. yeah, i know who he is. who is she? that's their lawyer. why didn't you tell me she was hot? because it's not relevant. it is to me. why? because she's hot. you must be the infamous harvey specter. you must be. evan smith. have to admit, when i saw your name was evan, i thought you were a man. and i have to admit, when i saw your name was harvey, i thought you were a man. i think i'm in love. i think you are too. okay, can we get this over with? we sure can. i don't even know how you have any questions at all, given our last meeting. we just have a few. mr. mcintyre, before the derailment, liberty rail conducted tests on the heat sensors on its trains. is that correct? of course we did. and why was that? we run tests on all our systems. it's routine. and the finding of that report is that there were no problems with the heat sensors. are you going to just ask questions that you already know the answers to? it's routine. there weren't any problems with the sensors. and do you routinely replace the heat sensors? yes. we replace them every five years as part of our regularly scheduled maintenance. and when was the last regularly scheduled maintenance? that would be two years ago. and you wouldn't fix something that wasn't broken, right? of course not. i'm not in the business of wasting money, gentlemen. i'm a bit confused. if you're not in the business of wasting money and there was nothing wrong with those sensors, then why did you just replace all of them? they didn't replace all of them. i think we'd like your client to answer that question. you're in a bit of a pickle, richard. you don't know whether to say you did or you didn't. of course, you could roll the dice with your own life just like you did with other people's. the truth is, it doesn't matter, because you already said on camera you didn't replace those sensors. and we have these. where'd you get these? i'll tell you what i told joe henderson. it doesn't matter where they came from. it just matters that they're here. i need to talk to my client. that's a good idea. you should discuss how many zeros you're gonna write on that check. and one more thing. you're not only gonna write a check. you're gonna write a public admission because people died in that crash. that's not how this works. it's how it works today. you're really gonna force them to make a public admission? damn right, i am. who are you, mahatma gandhi? somebody has to be. you were too busy demanding a bunch of zeros. well, i was just looking out for you. those suits don't pay for themselves. no, they don't. mike, great job. you really stepped it up. thanks, harvey. i think you might be starting to come into your own too. really? every single game? no, just the playoffs. two sips? two sips. no more, no less. any beer? oh, no, not any beer. miller lite. miller lite? what? but she's a queen. what can i tell you? she got it from her dad. look, if the giants are in the playoffs and jessica doesn't take two sips of miller lite after every single first down, she thinks they're gonna lose, and there's no talking her out of it. and those happen a lot, right? first downs? they sure do. so what is she like when she's drunk? well, that's a conversation for another time. ooh. i so feel you, bro. you know, i got to say, louis, i almost feel bad about pulling that prank on you. don't feel bad. it was a pretty good prank. okay. one more? only if you tell me more about what jessica's like at home. no, screw that, i want you to tell me what she was like back when it was pearson hardman. done. hey. hey. you're heading out for the night? in a few minutes. want to grab a drink? celebrate? i can't. why not? not that it's any of your concern, but i'm having drinks with evan smith. what? you got her number? no, she called me. oh, she asked for your number? no, she didn't have to. you gave it to her. it was on that subpoena. i know what's gonna be on your subpoena. what does that even mean? you know what it means. sure as hell do. you wanted to see me? i did. i take it you heard about liberty rail. i did. see? no harm, no foul, no mass exodus of clients. i'm glad. what's on your mind, jessica? you don't seem. i know you told scottie about mike ross. how'd you know? i didn't till just now. jessica. i'm not mad. i just want to know what made you want to tell her. what difference does that make? because i want to tell jeff the truth about mike ross too. what changed between now and when you fed him that louis bullshit? nothing's changed. i just don't want to lie to him anymore. he told you he loved you, didn't he? when the hell did you start figuring shit like that out? i didn't till just now. then answer my question. what made you decide to tell scottie? that's not what you really want to know. what you want to know is if i wish i told her sooner. do you? yes, i do. hey. hey, rachel, what can i do for you? i just wanted to come by and say thank you. for what? oh, come on, donna. mike told me you saved the day. oh, well, you know, after i saved those kids from that burning building, i had a little extra time, so. well, then maybe you should take the rest of the night off. and why is that? because that's what superheroes do. macallan . you got great taste. surprised i called? like i said, you got great taste, but let me be clear. you want to talk settlement, i can't do it without mike ross. i'm definitely not here to talk settlement. good, because there are things i can do without him, exceptionally. i want to show you a little video. what, did you dig up footage from my high school championship? because that'll make this too easy. afraid not. that's your secretary unlawfully gathering evidence, which means there will be no settlement of any kind. and tomorrow, i'm sending this to the district attorney. enjoy your drink, handsome. jessica. jeff, there's something i need to tell you. there's something i need to tell you too. what's going on? what's going on is i just had drinks with louis, you know, as a favor to you. turns out he's not so great at holding his liquor. what did he do? no, he didn't do anything. you did. i don't. you see, we were actually bonding when i suddenly remembered what he had done to you, and i. well, i wanted to make sure that no one ever did that to you again. so i asked him how he found out about daniel hardman's embezzlement, and he started with the words, it was two years ago. jeff, i can explain. you can always explain, but that just means your whole story about how louis got his name on the door is bullshit. and i came here to tell you the truth. more bullshit! then let me tell you now. don't you get it? we're past that now. i don't want to know! jeff. in fact, i never really wanted to know, i just. i just wanted you to tell me. but now, no matter what you tell me, i won't ever believe it's the truth. jeff, let me in. it's over, jessica. it's done. we're done