 now i want the respect that comes with it. meaning? i want one of harvey's clients. my clients are my clients, and if you don't get out of my office in the next three seconds, something's gonna happen between you and me, and i guarantee it won't end with you keeping all of your teeth. avery mckernon was the first client i ever brought into the firm. and they win, like me. they know trevor isn't in the class, so they know he couldn't have been the one to steal the test. i'm not going to expel your friend. thank you, sir. i. there's just one thing. i'm gonna call harvard. believe me when i tell you you're never going there. remember this? no, you don't. because you can't remember something you never knew. you can't fire me. why would i fire you when i can break you? you see, i'm going to bury you under a mountain of shit so big, you're going to be begging me to take it off. first of all, give me that manhattan and go get yourself a drink a man would order. come back here in minutes, and if i still remember who you are, i'll be shocked. okay, so why are we really here? i mean, you didn't just bring me out to talk about khaleesi. i did. paul porter says i look like her translator. he's a throner? though he says i'm a less attractive version of her translator. okay, you're just trying to get me to say that you're hotter than her. am i? you're way hotter. but she has that accent. fair point. you know, look, the reason that i brought you here is to tell you that i know that you told louis that i got katrina a job. look, i. relax, i'm not mad at you. but i do remember you being the person who told me not to force things that weren't meant to be. rachel, just because a person gives advice doesn't mean that they have to follow that same advice. that's one of the core principles outlined in the book of donna. seriously, though, i didn't mean to tell louis. it just came out. i'm sorry. like i said, it's fine. he actually ended up asking if we could be friends again. and? and i told him that things would never be the same between us unless he forgave mike. and what did he say? he said he couldn't do it. that's easy. the jumper over ehlo. wrong, the switch hand layup over perkins and green. i'm surprised at you, harvey. the ehlo jumper was a game winner. the layup was a statement. i can do whatever i want. i own this league. are you talking about jordan or yourself now? is there a difference? a big difference, which brings me to why i'm here. you can't do whatever you want, harvey. you want me to make things right with louis. he made things right between jeff and me. so i'm supposed to kiss his ass forever because of that? no, you're supposed to make peace. jessica, i'm willing to make peace, but that's never gonna happen. why not? because louis is never gonna forgive mike. then figure out a way to make him forgive mike. donna, how many times have i told you i want you out front? i'm the only associate with a secretary. it would be nice if people could see my secretary. well, then maybe your next secretary can figure out where to put this without coming into your office. you're kidding? not kidding. you didn't forge this? i am a lot of things, but i am not a monster. i would do that to neither michael nor you. oh, so he's michael now? well, i'm donna to him. he's michael to me, which is what i told his airness when he called. wait a second. you're not kidding. he signed with me? well, technically, he signed with me. holy shit, donna. we have to celebrate tonight. oh, i'm gonna celebrate. you, on the other hand, are having drinks with louis. what? we've been over this. whenever louis asks to have drinks with me, the answer's always no. listen to the words that i'm saying. you are getting drinks with louis tonight. fairchild's retiring? fairchild's dead. that's almost as good as the jordan news. eh, not to fairchild. who gives a shit about fairchild? the real tragedy is i have to get drinks with louis. which is why i got you a secluded restaurant with a table in the back where no one will see you. and you'll call a half an hour in and say there's an emergency. already in place, and if i can't get through, then i'll just have the waiter spill drinks all over louis. you could have that done? oh, please. i could have louis held captive in a tibetan monastery if i wanted to. yeah, i don't think you have that. now get the hell out of your office. i got work to do. hmm. excuse me. can you tell me where jim o'donnell's office is? that depends. what do you know about immigration law? what, are we talking visas, or are you trying to process a labor certification? you know about immigration law? doesn't everybody? okay, tough guy, what do you think about my strategy on this? hmm. i think it's a winner. why is that? because everyone knows gonzalez versus state of maryland was a kick ass precedent, but your case is better. it was a kick ass precedent, but i'm not sure that my case is better. oh, it is. well, what about viteri versus. trust me, it's better. viteri needed magic dust and a sympathetic judge to win. have we met? nope. but i'm mike, by the way. claire. are you sure? because you look very familiar. oh, that's probably because i've been delivering packages to your office for the last two months. but you haven't given me the time of day, because you didn't think i was smart enough for you. it's . wait. that worked? it's working so far, but i'm gonna need to know your full story if it's gonna keep working. well, i'll tell you the full story once you give me your phone number. i'll give you my number when i know the full story. how about this? i'll tell you everything you want to know at dinner tomorrow night. in that case, i'll show you where jim o'donnell's office is. jim o'donnell's office? where do you think i just came from? i need you do something for me. okay, what is it? never mind what it is. unless you want to go back to whatever you were doing before i hired you, you'll be here at a.m. this is the address for your car club. oh, yeah, your memory. i'd remember this even if i had your memory. it was right before our first case together. you're right, mckernon motors. so this time be on time and put your seat belt on, because we're about to take a trip down memory lane. see the money, wanna stay for your meal get another piece of pie for your wife everybody wanna know how it feel everybody wanna see what it's like i'll even eat a bean pie, i don't mind me and missy is so busy, busy making money all right suits x fork in the road original air date on february , all step back, i'm 'bout to dance the greenback boogie sync, corrected by elderman elder man. morning, sunshine. what are you. i think you call it a prunie. congratulations, donna told you my favorite breakfast drink, but what does that have to do with the price of tea in antarctica? donna also told me that you were pissed, because you found out i gave you a client i didn't want in the first place. hmm. and you think this is gonna make up for that? no, but i think giving you of mckernon motors will. what's the catch? the catch is, you and i are about to take a road trip to their corporate headquarters right now. you serious? i don't joke about mckernon motors, and you know that as well as i do. to fairchild. to fairchild. god rest his soul. screw his soul. you know how they say heaven just got another angel ? they ain't saying it now. why do you keep checking your phone? no reason. i just. please, i'm not an idiot. we've been here minutes, and in minutes, donna's gonna call with some preplanned emergency. louis, that's not. look, why do you think i used fairchild's retirement to get you to have drinks with me? because you knew i thought it would never happen? because he doesn't have an heir apparent. louis, if you're thinking what i think you're thinking. hardman's not gonna make one of us senior partner. i'm not talking about one of us. i'm talking about both of us convincing hardman that two kick ass junior partners are worth as much as one new senior partner. louis, that is the best idea you've had since i've known you. yeah? here's another one. when did you come up with this one? when you were in the bathroom wasting minutes of our half hour. don't you have to get that? no, i don't. let's drink to this. asshole. that was donna, wasn't it? trevor, this is so stupid. it's not stupid, dickhead. i want you to see it for the first time from the middle of the room. it's your apartment, assface, and don't even think about giving me a wet willie. you suck the fun out of everything. go ahead. open your eyes, dickfoot. dickfoot ? i was gonna use assface. it's all i could think of. how do you even manage in the world? are you just gonna stand there with your your eyes closed and mock my dickfoot ? i'm definitely not gonna open them to see your dickfoot. that's a good point. i wouldn't do that either. go ahead. open your eyes. wow. holy shit. i thought you were getting a studio. yeah, i was going to, but then i realized we can't both live in a studio. what? welcome to casa evans and ross. trevor, i can't afford half this rent. that's the best part. don't worry about it. i'm gonna pay for your whole first year. no, you're not. i can't let you do that. michael, i start my new job on tuesday. on top of that, i have my friends and family business on the side. that doesn't mean i'm gonna take charity from you. look, are you gonna make me say it? it's not charity. i graduated, and you didn't, because you took the fall for something i did. i owe you. okay, i'll think about it. all right, in the meantime, think about this. ahh. no, i can't. i got a date tonight. all right. wow, clubfoot, mustache, all of the above? first dickfoot and then clubfoot? are words with foot all you've got now? all right, smart guy, describe her with one of your sat words. bigfoot. that's what i'm talking about. for the record, she's really hot. let me get this straight. instead of promoting an existing partner, you want me to make both of you junior partners. well, not make us. we've earned it. earned partnership status? that's a pretty bold statement coming from two fifth years. not just any fifth years. we're the best fifth years this firm has ever seen, and you know it. may i inquire whose idea this was? it was both of ours. i was louis'. that's generous of you to give him credit. it was generous of him to come to me with the idea. the truth is, i wasn't gonna make anyone partner. but i do like admire your gumption. so here's what i'm willing to do. i will advance one of you if you prove to me which one it should be. no, see, that's the whole point. we came in as a package deal. you came in with a proposal. i'm giving you a counter, and it's take it or leave it. what sort of proof are we talking about? let's just say mckernon motors is in play, and landing them could go a long way to making your case. no way. we're not gonna. all right, daniel. you want mckernon? i'll get you mckernon. we're going to mckernon motors, not your senior prom. why can't we just take the car service? because we're going to an engine manufacturer. we need to show up with a bad ass car. how about this little bad boy right here? that's no good. why the hell not? because it's not just the two of us. what do you mean? you son of a bitch. you said you and i are going up there. you lied to me. because if i didn't, you would have never agreed to come. there is no way i'm going. yes, you are. i don't care if i have to tie you to the roof. by the time we get to mckernon, you and mike are gonna work your shit out. i can't believe you did that. the plan was to present a united front. and we did, and he didn't go for it. then you stab me in the back? i didn't stab you in the back. i took what he gave us. he didn't give us anything, harvey. he pitted us against each other. louis, we've been pitted against each other since day one. what are you talking about? how many of the associates we started with do you think are gonna make partner? i don't give a shit about the other associates. we toasted to making partner together. i don't make the rules, louis. hardman does. and as much as we say he's an asshole, i respect him for at least telling us the deal out loud. you want something out loud? i'm gonna give you something out loud. no way on earth am i gonna let you land mckernon motors. hey, what the hell? what the hell what? this isn't a joyride, louis. you don't want to talk, you're gonna sit in silence until you're ready to talk. well, you can make me sit in silence all you want, but you can't make me work it out with him. then what can, louis? excuse me? you worked it out with donna and rachel. you lied to malone for jessica. what's it gonna take to work it out with me? well, i forgave those people, because they were victims infected with the disease known as mike ross. now i'm stuck in a car with patient zero. okay, outbreak, patient zero is the first person actually infected with the disease, not the disease itself, and for your information, i'm stuck in the same car as you. at least you don't have to look at the back of your own stupid, fat, balding head. what's so goddamn funny? you two are finally talking. i think you earned a little music. that's it? yeah. all you have to do is pick one of two characters. and whichever character i don't pick is removed from film history forever? it's like they never existed. it's a piece of cake. okay, han solo or indiana jones? i'm out. what's the problem? you just said it was gonna be a piece of cake. the problem is, you just picked the two greatest characters of all time, so. you're right about that. i'm sorry. let me start with something easier for you. all right. butch or sundance? mm, check, please. yeah, we're done. no. this is really nice. yeah, i'm having a really good time too. so when do i get to hear the answer to what you do besides being a bike messenger? who says i do anything? look, mike, there's nothing wrong with being a bike messenger, but i'm serious about my life. i'm not going to law school just to cash out. i really want to help people. bike messengers don't help people? no, not in the way that a man i want to be in a relationship with does. well, then today is your lucky day. i knew it. where do you go? mm mm, you first. where do you go? nyu. columbia. i win. good morning, jessica. hi, daniel. i still haven't received. this year's budget? i was just on my way to give it to you. and i thought maybe you hadn't gotten around to it because you were too busy pitting harvey against louis. you disapprove. i don't mind a little healthy competition. but i do mind the empty promise of partnership. what makes you so sure there's no reward at the end? the last time we discussed this, you said harvey wasn't ready. and you said louis wasn't. well, i'm giving them both the chance to prove it. so partnership is on the table. partnership was already on the table. what makes you so sure it's gonna be harvey? because harvey will do whatever it takes to win. if doing whatever it takes is the criteria, my money is on louis. what are you talking about? i think we should continue this conversation in my office. hi, i've got a delivery for a zoltan freastmeisterson. i'm afraid there's no one in this office with that name. i'm afraid you're mistaken. really? yeah. because i'm willing to bet that there's no one on this planet with that name. okay, fine, but if you could just point me towards. kumquat mcgillicuddy's office, i'll be on my way, because i certainly did not bike down here with two fictitious deliveries just to tell you what a great time i had last night. good, because i have a lot of work to do. so, if you could please just hop on that little bike of yours. claire? yeah. when you're finished flirting with quicksilver here, you might want to get down to ins. hector suarez just got taken in. shit. his visa's expired. they're gonna send him back to the dominican republic. wait. maybe i can help. no offense, i don't see how you can. no, no, no, nathan, he's not just a bike messenger. he's in law school. really? where are you in law school? columbia. and he happens to know visas better than either one of us. well, i really can't pay you, so. no, i don't need any money. i just want to help. all right, columbia, be my guest. got a hearing tuesday morning, a.m. mike, that is amazing. thank you. oh, no, don't thank me yet. i haven't even done any. um, this might not be relevant, but i actually saved. kumquat mcgillicuddy's life this morning, so. i'm gonna go do some work. thank you. mr. mckernon, harvey specter. mr. specter, would you mind telling me why i have two different pearson hardman lawyers on my schedule today? i don't know, but after this, you won't need to meet the other one. you're cocky. i'm right. you're also traveling a little light. where's your powerpoint presentation? i don't need a powerpoint presentation. why is that? because every lawyer in the city has tried to dazzle you, and you're still looking for a date to the big dance, because they don't know what you're looking for. what exactly am i looking for? loyalty. you're right. i built this company from the ground up, and everybody that started with me is still here. and i know why. you don't downsize in the bad times. they stick with you in the good times. and no other lawyer has figured that out. not a single one. well, i'm the one, avery, which is why i know you don't want me dumping you for a bigger client down the line. how do i know you won't do that? because that's not the way i work. well, it's a hell of a nice sentiment. but how do i know you're not full of shit? i'm glad you asked, because here's my powerpoint presentation. okay. i have a hearing tomorrow against fletcher engines. you win that, you're my lawyer. ok, just don't change lanes. don't change lanes. don't do this. great. okay, you know what? this is ridiculous. you drive like a savage animal. louis, be a man and suck it up. suck it up? i'm sitting in the death seat. fine. i'll pull over, and you can sit in the back with mike. hey, i'm not sitting in the back with a fraud, and before you even think it, you're not putting him up here and sticking me back there. then what do you want, louis? because there is no way in hell i'm letting you behind the wheel of this car. it's crystal goddamn clear. you and i sit in the back, and he chauffeurs the both of us. whoa, no. even if harvey would agree to that, which i doubt. shut the hell up. you're not talking. you don't get to refuse. i'm not refusing, louis. i don't know how to drive. holy shit. you wanted to see me? uh, yes. i heard you did well with avery mckernon. well, then you heard wrong, because i killed it with avery mckernon. congratulations, harvey. thank you, daniel. you're welcome. unfortunately, we can't represent. mckernon motors after all. why not? well, it turns out fletcher engines wants to sign with us. because they found out i'm about to land mckernon. yes, and they're three times the size of mckernon motors. well, i don't care how big they are. i'm not dropping my client. yes, you are. this was your plan all along. of course it was. that's how the world works. i don't give a shit how the world works. i gave my word to avery mckernon. watch yourself, harvey. i haven't gotten where i am by watching myself, daniel. and i don't appreciate being used as a stalking horse. well, you may not appreciate it, but let me remind you, you work for me. and i'm giving you the chance to show me you understand that. let me remind you you said partnership was on the table. i'm gonna hold you to that, and so will jessica. hey, fart taster. i thought you were coming over. what, nothing? it's a classic. i'm implying your job is to literally taste. hey, trevor, i'm in the middle of something, so i'll come over later, okay? in the middle of what? that girl i told you about, she interns at a legal clinic, and i am helping her with a case. dickfoot gave you homework? okay, first of all, from now on, her name is claire. and second of all, this is important, so. dude, what the hell are you talking about? i might have told her that i'm in law school. holy shit. you will do anything to get laid. i am not trying to get laid. i really like this girl, and i have zero chance with her if all i am is a bike messenger. yeah, well, you're definitely gonna have no chance if she finds out that you lied to her. trevor, i don't want to talk about this anymore. you don't really want to talk about anything anymore. it's about the apartment, isn't it? yes it's about the apartment. okay, you want the truth? i haven't given you an answer because of grammy. you think i didn't know that? then you know she's never forgiven you for what happened in college, and she is never, ever going to let me live with you. then explain to her that this is my way of making up for what i did in college. that is never gonna work. you know what, michael? if you're gonna do all of this for some girl you just met, maybe it's time you stood up to grammy for me. how'd it go against fletcher engines? you cut them off at the knees or put them in the ground? they put me in the ground, and on top of that, it was in front of avery mckernon. you lost in court? i didn't just lose. i looked like a fool. harvey, what happened? the general counsel for fletcher engines knew every move i was gonna make before i even made it. how could he. because hardman must have tipped him off. you really think he would do that? i wouldn't have yesterday, but i sure as hell do today. then you have to go to jessica. and say what? hardman's managing partner. she's not. i don't have any proof, and i never will. well, then what are you gonna do? i don't know, but i have less than hours to dig through , pages of patent law. if only there was somebody in the office who was an expert on patent law. donna, i am not going to louis. he'll never help me. well, that's too bad, because if you can't figure out how to patch things up with louis, then you don't deserve avery mckernon or that partnership. what's all this? uh, a grandson can't order in and set a table for his grandmother? a grandson can do whatever he wants. but the answer to your question is no. you haven't even heard what it is yet. i know what it is, because i've been waiting for it since that kid graduated, and you are not gonna live with him. that boy is the reason you got kicked out of school. you're the one that told me to tell the dean the truth. that was before i knew it would cost you graduating. and he's trying to make it up to me. he's gonna pay for my whole first year's rent. that will not make up for putting your whole life into a tailspin. it's a head start. no, it's not a head start! that boy is gonna drag you back down with him! grammy, i'm never gonna let that happen! god damn it! i forbid it! i'm sorry, michael. i lost my temper. but i know what he does to you, and i know he'll always be the same. has it occurred to you that maybe i'm not the same? what's changed? i met someone. and i'm gonna figure out a way to finish school, and. and then i'm gonna go to law school. good. then do it from here. what's on your mind, mike? you look lost in thought. i was just thinking about my grandmother. we took a train trip to d.c. once. we played i spy. that's a nice story, mike, but we are not playing i spy. i'll play. it'll remind me of dominating esther on our trips to see our smelly aunt frida. all right, if it will get you and mike talking, sure. i spy a fraud who probably never even knew his grandmother. all right, god damn it, you got a problem with me, take it up with me, but don't ever talk about my grandmother again. oh, i forgot, the poor orphan from new york city who i should feel sorry for because he never learned to drive. i'm telling you, watch yourself. why? because i hurt your feelings? louis! i don't care. for all i know, you're probably not even an orphan. it sure as hell wouldn't be the first time a con man tried to make that claim. that's enough. no, it isn't. yes, it is. pull the car over right now. i'm gonna beat the shit out of him. hey, you got a minute? oh, wait. let me turn my back, so i can give you the right angle to. you were right. we should have stuck together. i get it. you need my help, because you got your ass wiped in court this morning. you're right. i did get my ass kicked this morning, but it wasn't a fair fight. what are you talking about? hardman accessed my computer and fed the other side my game plan. okay, i'm still waiting for the part where i'm supposed to give a shit. hardman did it because i refused to dump mckernon for fletcher after i gave him my word. and why should i help you when you couldn't live up to your word to me? i did live up to my word. we went to daniel. oh, bullshit. no, it's not bullshit. i welcomed your idea with open arms, and by the way, when he asked whose idea it was, i gave you the credit. you see, harvey, that's the part you will never understand. i didn't want the credit. i wanted us to be a team. then let's be a team right now. but you don't want to be a team. you want me to help you get mckernon so you can make partner. i want you to help me so i can keep my word to avery mckernon. and when i become partner, i'll keep my word to you. what the hell word is that? that someday what you wrote on that napkin goes up on the goddamn wall. you seem to have done a lot of work here, mike. oh, it's no big deal. it is a big deal. mike found a loophole in the immigration act of , and it's gonna blow you away. i don't know about that, but it may help hector suarez stay in the country. that's great. and you're more than welcome to stay and watch. unfortunately, claire, i need you to run back to the office. marshall called in sick. i need someone to handle the walk ins, so. okay. call me. tell me how it goes. yeah. what the hell are you doing? that's. gonna keep hector suarez in the country? yeah. yeah, nothing's gonna keep him in the country. so what i'm going to do is i'm gonna buy him some time so he can get his affairs in order, and then i'm gonna give his children a chance to stay. i'm just. i'm. i'm sorry. are you jealous of me and claire or. hey, look, i'm not jealous, and i was waiting for her to leave to save you the embarrassment. the embarrassment of what? that's good work. i'm not talking about the work. i'm talking about your bike messenger by day, law student by night bullshit. all right, you don't know what you're talking about. what are you gonna tell me next? your roommate is a stripper who's in medical school? tell me right now. i call columbia, your story holds up. that's what i thought. forget who i am, and take a look at that folder. this is a man's life. don't touch me. if you know what's good for you, you'll stay the hell away from claire. daniel. did you know that some of these species can live up to years? fascinating. did you know fletcher engines is picking up the pieces? i guess congratulations are in order. i not here for a pat on the back. i'm here to tell you you're making me partner. partner? i never said signing mckernon was the key to making partner. yes, you. all i said was landing them could go a long way toward making your case. bullshit. you said partnership was on the table. and i said i was gonna hold you to it. and i'm going to right now. you don't hold me to anything. but i did say partnership was on the table, and it is. just not for you. what are you talking about? well, i can't very well make you partner after i just told louis i'm making him partner. what? you don't get it, do you? this isn't about bringing in business. this is about figuring out who would do whatever it takes. i did whatever it took. you didn't do a thing. you had the chance to triple our business, and all you had to do was take a knee. you mean bend a knee. yes, that's exactly what i mean. but you're an arrogant little boy who would rather win than get in line. well, what the hell did louis do to get in line? he did whatever it took. please get away from me. claire, wait. nathan told me everything. just let me explain, okay? no, explain what. that you're a sociopath? i'm not a sociopath. i'm the same guy that you hit it off with. no, you're not. you lied to me. yes, i am, and i didn't mean to lie to you, okay? i was gonna tell you the truth. then why didn't you? because you said you wanted to be with a guy who was doing something good with his life, and i wasn't. so what, now you're here to tell me that all of a sudden, you want to dedicate your life to helping people or some other lie like that? it's not a lie, and what i did would have helped hector suarez. yeah, but you only did it. claire, please, you have to believe me. after i met you, i decided to get my shit together. i am trying to get my shit together. okay, mike, you know what i hate more than guys who don't have their shit together? it's guys who lie about getting their shit together. claire. louis, fill up the tank. i'll be back. well? well, what? you heard what he said. fill up the tank. yeah, i did hear what he said. he said, louis, fill up the tank. well, where i come from, it's people who didn't go to college who fill up gas tanks. yeah, and where i come from, if you take another step towards me. oh, what, the tough kid from the city is gonna beat my ass? louis, i'm telling you right now. you ruined my life. you ruined my firm. louis! you son of a bitch. wait. harvey. tell me right now you weren't the one that gave fletcher engines my game plan. hardman told me he wasn't gonna make you partner anyway. and once he offered it to me, all i had to do was. sell me out. how is what i did any different than you going after. mckernon motors in the first place? if you don't understand that on your own, you never will. so, from now on, you stay on your side of the yard. i'll stay on mine. no, harvey, listen to me. you told me you would fight to get our names on the wall once you got on the other side. i can do the same for you. did you hear what i just said? i don't want you doing shit for me. oh, so it would be okay if you were the one who got there first? it would have been okay if you got there first fair and square, because then i would have believed you when you said you wanted to be a team. i do want to be a team, harvey. that's why i helped you after. no, you don't! you don't want to be a team. you just want to have it both ways, because you're a disloyal rat. you always have been, and you always will, no matter what it says on your door. well, like you said, we've been pitted against each other since day one. you asked how many of the associates we started with would make partner. well, you know what? i don't give a shit about the other , because i'm the one who did. i'm the one who did. and now get the hell out of my face, because i have work to do. you know he did that on purpose, right? did what on purpose? he asked you to fill the tank because he knew what you'd do. knew what i would do? what about what you would do? he knew that too. louis. you never even said you were sorry. i am sorry, louis. i'm sorry that i lied to you. i'm not a con man, louis. every single other thing i ever told you was true. want to know something that i've never even admitted to myself? i never learned to drive for the same reason i never went to law school. both my parents were killed in a car accident. and ever since then, i've never been able to. get behind the wheel. and then harvey gave me a license, and i took it. you were years old. i mean, you must have felt so alone. i thought you said you didn't believe i was an orphan. i looked it up. i had to once i found out that you never went to law school. you mean once you found out that i'm a fraud. you're not a fraud, mike. you just never went to law school. okay, frazier, you get a grape. ali, i got you a fruit punch. you two work your shit out? i'll take that as a yes. let's get the hell out of here. i should never have lied to her. oh, screw her, man. if she doesn't like you for who you are, she doesn't deserve you. it's not claire's fault. it's mine. i know you were into her and everything, but trust me, there are plenty of other fish in the sea. you don't know that. for all you know, i'm never gonna meet another girl like her again. michael. trevor, if i'm gonna have to listen to whatever you're about to say, i'm gonna need a joint first. come on, i thought you were trying to turn your life around. i'll turn my life around tomorrow. but tonight i'm a bike messenger, so. dude. trevor. all right. fine. and i know grammy doesn't want you living here, but you can crash here tonight if you want. donna. something wrong? why would something be wrong? because i don't believe you've ever been in my office before. no, nothing's wrong. and i know it's not my place, but i'm here to tell you that i think you're making a mistake. is this about me not giving people off for columbus day? you know this isn't about that. harvey laid it on the line with daniel, and you didn't have his back. donna, i've had harvey's back since the day i met him. for your information, when i found out what daniel was up to, i had him guarantee partnership was on the table. and then you let him give it to the wrong man. that is on harvey, not on me. what are you talking about? daniel was worried that harvey couldn't put the firm's best interests ahead of his own, and harvey proved him right. or maybe you're just telling yourself that because you don't want to stand up to daniel hardman. donna, there's a reason why you are where you are and i am where i am, and that is because one of us sees the bigger picture. you knew about fletcher engines? what i know is that harvey's time will come. and if this little incident gets him to think about other people for a change, then i'll take it. you're up early. i'm up early, because i couldn't sleep. where we you all night? you know where i was. i was staying at my new apartment. i thought we'd settled this. you settled it. i didn't. i'm telling you, that kid. grammy, for as long as i can remember, you've been calling him that kid or that boy or worse. his name is trevor. and he's my best friend. look, i'm gonna do this thing with our without your blessing, but. it sure would be nice to have it. okay, michael. i'm not gonna lie to you and pretend i approve, but. you're a grown man, and i respect your decision. i love you, grammy. i love you too. thank you. i believe that's all i need to know. thank you for your time, ms. pearson. i will wait to hear from you. oh, one more thing. does your father know you came to me for a job? i i. did you really think i didn't know you were robert zane's daughter? is that why you're interviewing me? because if it is, i would like to remove myself from consideration. if you don't want to work for your father, that's your business. i'm hiring you because i like what i see. hiring me? you start monday, if that's not too much trouble. i will be the first one in. aren't you gonna ask me why i don't want to work with my father? i know why. i have a dad just like yours. he has his own law firm? he's a surgeon. but it's the same damn thing. how are we on time? we're perfect. but i'm not going in there. you two are. what are you talking about? i said i was giving you of mckernon. i didn't say i was keeping the other . oh, so you finally realized they need an upgrade in representation. easy, frazier. you'd still be out cold at that gas station if i hadn't saved your ass. okay, i would have gotten out. eventually. not from where i was standing. i'm slippery. i told you. i wrestled in high school. i checked on that. he did. see? oh, and now you're fighting for him? okay, i guess my job here is done. wait. where are you going? i'm taking the car back to the city. well, what the hell are we supposed to do? ray's waiting on the other side of the parking lot, isn't he? he'll drive you two back when you're done. wait. you know what? i have a better idea. how about you take ray, we take the car, and i teach mike how to drive on the way home? you'd actually do that? yeah, i would. no way. you don't trust me? i don't trust you as far as i can throw you. you're a goddamn fraud. that's what i said. harvey, seriously. come on, i promise. okay, i know you will. louis, you make one dent in this car, mike's back on the street, and your name's off the door. you think he was serious about what he just said? okay, well, i'm just a little nervous, 'cause i feel like i drank that power drink, and it has a lot of sodium in it. actually, it's like drinking a hot dog, but the doctor says it raises my blood pressure, so. i'm gonna need you to let me do the talking in there